Noctus Cochlear was the mastermind
behind the unprecedented
chaos at the White Wolf's Den.
Right now,
the Association is holding a meeting
about dealing with the aftermath.
Regarding the confiscated
items from this incident...
Could we maybe get the Akasha golem?
And the something-water? Those two things?
By water, do you maybe
mean the Malice Eater?
Yes, yes. That, please.
What do you want with it?
What would you need the Malice Eater for?
Isn't it obvious?
For drinking.
For drinking... you say?
Are you serious right now?
Huh? What?
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Amid the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony,
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
Zebrudia's Association is just up ahead.
Arnold!
Don't worry,
everybody will soon know the Falling Fog!
Episode 10
I Want to Be Renowned in the Capital
"I Want to Be Renowned in the Capital."
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
I knew asking you was the right move.
I didn't get the golem, though.
That's too bad, but c'est la vie.
It's more than enough that
we got something "to drink."
That's getting old.
I'll take care of the handover, then.
Sure. I'll wait for you in the lobby.
Okay.
Hey,
do you have a second?
Crashing... Light...ning?
The second name of Arnold Hail.
He recently came to the capital
from Nebulanubes the Land of Fog.
He's a level 7 hunter.
You really haven't heard of him?
I mean, I'm not interested in all that.
You're pretty carefree, huh?
We're talking about a Dragon Slayer here—
someone who's taken down a thunder dragon.
If you put it that way,
I'm a Dragon Slayer, too.
Oh, yeah. You're right!
Well, either way, please don't
start trouble with him, okay?
I'll be counting on you.
There goes another Safety Ring.
But I will not yet leave this li-i-ife...
Huh?
Is it already that time of year?
The Zebrudian Auction.
A grandiose event held once a year.
Most of the items auctioned are relics,
so naturally,
the quality and quantity of relics flowing
into Zebrudia during this
time are off the charts.
I completely forgot.
I want to go, but I'm broke.
If all else fails,
I could borrow from Sitri...
No, wait.
Did I ever return what I
borrowed from her last time?
Krai, Krai, Krai?
You are...
Chloe.
Chloe Welter.
I'm usually over there at reception.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
She's Gark's niece.
Hard to believe they're related.
My uncle's been in a really good mood.
Did something happen?
Well...
There was something about some
Dragon Slayer or whatnot.
You mean the Crashing Lightning?!
That's Arnold Hail, from the Falling Fog!
Yeah, yeah!
Almond Oil, from Fallin' Love.
Thanks for waiting, Krai.
Sure.
See you later.
Y-Yes!
He's so dauntless...
So that's the Malice Eater?
Yes.
He's a very good boy.
Hey!
Yes?
You're new here, right?
Welcome, and thank you for coming!
It's pretty cute.
Isn't it dangerous?
Please don't worry.
I've trained it to not harm Krai or myself.
I-Is that so?
There, there!
Hey, now!
You stop that, Drink.
You mustn't bother Krai.
Wait, you're really going to call it that?
It's the name you gave him, after all.
Not that I meant to.
She said that it wouldn't hurt me.
So what was that, then?
That was just it snuggling up to me?
This is bad.
I need to charge my mana before
Drink snuggles me to death.
Sitri, when is Lucia getting back again?
Let me think...
It could be quite a while yet.
Actually, a strong swordsman phantom
appeared in the boss chamber...
Oh.
So that disease of Luke's
flared up again, huh?
Yes.
He insisted on going at it alone
until he can beat it...
Lucia and the others said
they'd stay as well.
I see.
I wish at least Lucia would come back...
That reminds me.
I forgot to give this to you.
This.
Huh.
What a classic Aspiration Manifest.
It's a relic that lets you
store a single spell.
I always carry around the one
Lucia gave me as a lucky charm.
So what's up with this?
You can have it.
I hope you'll put it on here.
Oh, okay.
Damn it!
That receptionist must have been blind!
Arnold is level 7!
It is what it is.
We're the outsiders here.
Eigh!
Let's enlighten them as to just what we can do.
A hero from the Land of Fog is
a hero in Zebrudia as well.
We'll let these hunters
know what we're made of.
That's right!
We're the Dragon Slayers of the Falling Fog!
This is the last time anyone from
this town looks down on us!
You're itching to show off your
skills, right, Arnold?
Yeah.
Krai...
Does that feel good?
Yup, yup, it does.
So, about charging my relics.
Most of them are out of mana,
and I'd like to get them all
topped up if possible.
But since there are just so many,
I'm reluctant to ask any
mage other than Lucia.
If that's so...
then I've got...
a good idea!
All of you here right now are very lucky.
Today, Krai suggested that we teach
you a special mage-training technique.
Huh?
These lessons differ from his
usual Thousand Trials,
so you need not fear death.
But there's much to gain!
Those who do this will all be able
to become mages on par with Lucia!
On par with Lucia?
There's a way to train to
get as powerful as her?
Count on Master to come
up with a plan like this.
She's selling it well, but I
have no idea what she's getting at.
So, what do you say?
Would anyone here be interested?
That is an intriguing offer.
Lapis. Kris.
I was not expecting members
of Starlight to be here.
What's with that look,
honestly, feeble human?!
Lapis is here, and you don't
even formally greet her, honestly?!
Apologize properly, honestly!
It's fine, Kris.
Dim-witted as he may be,
he is the clan master.
In human society, I suppose we
ought to follow human customs.
It's really hard to believe that he's
Lucia's older brother, honestly.
Starlight is a unique party made of
demi-humans called Noble Spirits.
Noble Spirits live for a long time
and are experts at magic,
Lapis Fulgor
Hunter level 6
but they casually look down on all
humans who are not great mages.
Kris Argent
Hunter level 3
Well, then, Sitri Smart.
Even for us Noble Spirits, Lucia
is someone special.
A human who overflows with magical talent.
Are you saying anyone can reach her level?
There is no training in this
world that could do that.
Lucia became the most
renowned mage in the capital
because of this training. Honestly.
Um...
I'll try it.
You sure about that?
That's the spirit, Marietta.
So I just need to charge it?
That's right.
Hey, what is this?!
It's taking forever to charge!
Please keep going.
It's done.
Now for the next one.
What?!
Here you go.
The amount of mana a mage possesses
greatly influences their skill.
One can generally increase their mana
from childhood to their mid-teens.
Which means that everyone
here is well past that stage.
Marietta!
Marietta?
As you can see, if you overuse your mana,
you reach this state of mana depletion.
I'm sure all of you here have
experienced this before.
But! This moment is actually your chance.
Since you've all reached the end
of your developmental stage,
you can no longer increase
your mana capacity normally.
But that's no reason to despair!
It's a known fact that during recovery
from a mana-depleted state,
one's mana capacity also
increases by a few percent.
An ultra-recovery, so to speak...
But that requires you to abuse
your mind to the absolute limit!
Ridiculous! Even we need time to
recover our mana, honestly.
This is in no way an efficient
way to train, honestly.
And that's where this comes in.
Hey, wai—
And as you can see, Marietta's mana
capacity has indeed increased!
By repeating this process over and over,
it becomes a viable way
to improve your abilities.
Huh? Lucia's been doing that all this time?
No pain, no gain.
Surely you're aware of that?
Kill, kill, kill.
Lucia really became that strong
through this training?
The power Lucia wields
doesn't come from talent.
It's from all the blood, sweat,
and tears she's shed,
and from her mana capacity!
And all the while she did this, she never
once let it show that she was suffering.
Speaking of, I've heard that
Starlight wants to scout Lucia...
But you're resting on your laurels for
being a race gifted with magic talent...
Perhaps that attitude is the reason
that Lucia isn't impressed?
That's so rude... honestly!
Kris.
We will not stand idly by and
let her humiliate us any further.
Yes, honestly!
Hey. Give me those relics
right now, honestly!
I'm going to charge all
of them right away, honestly!
Well, if you insist.
Kill, kill, kill.
Kill.
This is not much.
It shouldn't be a big deal, Kris.
Yes, honestly.
Here I go, honestly!
I-I'll do it, too.
Me, too!
I won't be left in the dust!
Me neither.
I'll do it.
Same!
Looks like the relics will all get charged.
Yes, yes.
And have you given it some thought?
It's not a bad deal for you.
I'm very honored,
but there are still things I must learn.
You mean from Thousand Tricks?
To think that there could be a
hunter that would rival you,
you who hail from the House of Rodin.
So be it.
We can wait for the right time
to discuss our exclusivity deal.
Which reminds me.
Have you already met with Earl Gladis?
Not yet...
Apparently, his daughter
has been looking for you.
Ark!
Lady Éclair.
Please make yourself comfortable.
It will take some time for her to emerge.
Ti.
My sister is treating you
horribly, isn't she?
Y-You're too close, Sitri.
You'd become stronger much faster
if you left her and joined me.
M-Master!
Sitri.
I was just joking.
Ti? Where's my towel?
Yes!
I'm bringing it right now!
Jeez.
I told you to get it ready.
What's this?
It's Krai!
Liz, put on some clothes!
Ouch... wait...
Your fingers... my eyes...
You're going to make Krai uncomfortable!
Please!
What? He's fine.
I'm not.
What brings you over?
Well...
I was thinking we could celebrate you
and Sitri coming back home safely.
Oh, that's so nice of you!
You stay away from him!
Si, stop getting in my way!
You need to stop!
Tino, you, too.
Huh? I'm invited, too?
The more the merrier, right?
Apologize!
Never!
We're treated like country
bumpkins no matter where we go.
How dare they?!
They're such a snobby bunch.
Eigh.
Is there anywhere to get
a drink around here?
Si... you...
You did something, didn't you?
There's no way I would get drunk this fast.
Please stop with the wild accusations.
Right, Ti?
I... I didn't see anything...
Thank you for waiting!
Please enjoy your stay!
Already tapping out?
Then I guess all of this will be your treat.
MaruP, over here!
What?!
Don't be so full of yourself!
Coming!
I can see through all your schemes.
I bet that whole Akashic
thing was all your doing!
You're way too drunk.
That golem was totally useless!
A little sturdy, but besides
that, it was ultra-weak!
That was because it hadn't been
trained in real combat yet!
Once I improve it a few times,
even you won't be able to—
Krai, did you hear that?!
Yes, yes. I certainly did.
Liz, I think you've had too much.
Hey, why are you on her side?!
Let's resume our drinking contest.
Or you can tap out like a loser if you want.
Bring it on!
And don't think you're going to win!
You're so weird.
No fighting, now.
Sitri, I bet the weird
accusations don't feel great.
We can call this even now, right, Liz?
Here you go, Liz.
H-Hold on...
Thank you!
I drank it all. Now it's your turn!
Go. Go, go!
Krai, aren't you just
taking advantage of me?
Huh?
You only shee me as a wallet, don'tcha?
D'you have any idea how
much money I've lent you?
Ten digits. Ten digits!
Yes, yes. That's so true.
Wait, ten digits?
I'm going to have you pay
me back with your body.
Hey!
Touching is forbidden!
What's your problem?!
Listen up!
We are the Falling Fog!
And don't you forget it!
And this is the hero of Land of Fog,
the Dragon Slayer known
as Crashing Lightning,
"Crashing Lightning"
Arnold Hail
Hunter level 7
Arnold Hail!
I'll enlighten you halfwits
here in the capital.
Arnold is level 7.
Seven?!
Seven...
I wonder if I could build
a new Killiam with that...
Arnold?
I feel like I've heard that name before.
Oh, well. Whatever.
Hey, booze and women.
Got it! Bring us booze and women!
Right here!
I've got booze and a woman right here!
Please, no!
Uh...
Liz, that's not fair.
Early bird gets the worm!
You want to drink with
a fine woman, correct?
I'll give you a special treat.
Go home, brat.
Don't be like that. Just drink up.
And the beer stein, too!
Hey, hey!
I'm gonna beat you
to a mushy, messy pulp!
You bitch!
You're so damn weak!
Are you really level 7?
All right!
Let's drink!
I-I'm so sorry.
This girl's had way too much.
Come on, Liz.
Tino, Sitri. We're going home.
Yes, sir!
Triumphantly,
Oh, sorry. Looks like I forgot my wallet.
the Falling Fog came to the capital
to make a name for themselves.
Could I borrow some money?
But look at them now!
What a sad state of affairs!
The world is vast, Arnold Hail.
You've got this next time,
our Dragon Slayer, Arnold Hail!
All in the next episode!
Please tune in again next time!
By: MaruP-chang
A heavy blow to the head in the
pub, what a shocking shock!
Enraged, she caught him unaware.
He's mad she got 'em.
I bet they're really good hunters.
Or maybe not?
Being treated like noobs and can't sleep...
We hate it!
Next time on Let This Grieving Soul Retire.
Episode 11
The Falling Fog Wants Revenge
Retire!
"The Falling Fog Wants Revenge."
Revenge!